family health insurance is the need of
the earth
lifestyle diseases and medical expenses
are rising are you looking for the best
way to protect yourself and your family
icici lombard is redefining the way you
stay protected
the icici lombard complete health
insurance comes with options for you to
choose from
all the options are packed with
comprehensive features for enhanced
protection choose coverage for your
family health insurance as per your
needs and get the advantage of features
such as
claim protector super no claim bonus
unlimited reset benefit
some insured protector
additional some insured protector
worldwide cover emergency assistance
apart from the basic hospitalization day
care and related pre and post expenses
under the policy
let's look at how the claim protector
feature is beneficial in case you opt
for this cover we will cover the
expenses for the irdai's list of
non-payable items under the policy too
what's more
you get a super no claim bonus too
for every claim-free year you will be
rewarded with a bonus which is equal to
fifty percent of your sum in short
the maximum you can accumulate as bonus
is hundred percent for some insured
options of up to ten lakhs and up to two
hundred percent for some insured options
15 lakhs in above this product also
comes with some insured protector a
feature which guarantees an increase in
your coverage amount this is the cpr
inflation rate prevalent in our society
another key benefit is the unlimited
reset benefit
if the balance sum insured is
insufficient for subsequent claims in
the same year we will reset the coverage
amount up to 100 of your base sum in
short you can also get the advantage of
additional sum in short protector the
best part is you don't have to worry
while you're traveling abroad either the
worldwide cover ensures that
hospitalization expenses incurred abroad
shall be paid with a co-pay of 10
there is further emergency assistance
available too this includes
domestic road ambulance expenses
incurred on road ambulance services will
be covered
assistance for ambulance
delhi consultation
and more
did you know that 63 of healthcare
expenses are incurred on outpatient
services which are not covered in
traditional healthcare insurance
policies
icici lombard offers be fit
a comprehensive cashless outpatient
solution
it gives you coverage for tests
medicines and minor opd procedures
get physical and virtual doctor
consultations
a health management program and